



603011897



noelalarconpuerta@gmail.com



Dúrcal, Granada España

More information

- -Driving licenses A1, B
- Own vehicle
- Full availability

Languages

Spanish:

Native.

English:

Intermediate/basic level.

About Me

I define myself as a person eager to learn and start my professional career. I have 1.5 years of internship experience in the technology sector, providing customer service, repairing all types of computer systems, and managing servers in both Linux and Windows environments.

Social Media

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/noel-alar

Github:

github.com/SrNoelll

Noel Alarcón

Full Stack Developer
Microcomputer Systems and Network Technician

Tools and Technologies

- Java
- CSS
- Postman

- PHP
- SQL
- WordPress

- Python
- JSON
- SE0

- Bash
- XML
- Photoshop
- JavaScript
- Docker
- Blender 3D

- HTML
- Git/Github
- Office Suite

Work Experience

IT Technician in Computer Assembly and Repair

Megasur | September 2021 - May 2022

- Assembly and repair of equipment.
- Inventory management and control.

IT and Multimedia Systems Technician

Nopea | September 2022 - May 2023

- Management and administration of operating systems.
- Repair of various types of computer equipment.
- Customer service.
- Creation of audiovisual content using Blender 3D, Photoshop, and DaVinci Resolve.

Academic Background

I.E.S Alonso Cano Educational Center

Higher Level Technical Certificate in Web Application Development | Currently Enrolled

I.E.S Alonso Cano Educational Center

Intermediate Level Technical Certificate in Microcomputer Systems and Networks | September 2021 - May 2023

Fundations of Cybersecurity | Google

This course is part of the Google Cybersecurity Professional Certificate

Play It Safe: Manage Security Risks | Google

This course is part of the Google Cybersecurity Professional Certificate